Charles Mingus Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-44)
  - Manuscript Music (Box 1-29, Box 32-44)
    - Original Music Manuscripts (Box 1-28, Box 32-44)
      - Mingus dances. No. 9: Haitian fight song / by Charles Mingus and Alan Raph; Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings; ozalid copies also included.; Reference no.: 255.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles Raph, Alan (Box-folder 16/7-8)
      - Mingus dances. No. 9: Haitian fight song / by Charles Mingus and Alan Raph; Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 255.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles Raph, Alan (Box-folder 17/1-2)
      - Mingus dances. No. 9: Haitian fight song (#23)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 154. (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Mingus fingers. See also: Harris + Mingus fingers, Lead sheet; 1 p.; 29.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 151. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Mingus fingers (#7). See also: Harris + Mingus fingers, Full score; 19 leaves; 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil with copyist's markings in regular and colored pencil.; Reference no.: 051. (Box-folder 37/13)
      - Mingus fingers (#7). See also: Harris + Mingus fingers, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 051. (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Mingus's lo slo bluze., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink.; Reference no.: 050. (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Minor intrusion., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom: © January, 1960, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, N.Y.; Reference no.: 157. (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Minor intrusion., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 157. (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Miss Bliss., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil; cello part written in ink by Hugo Vianello.; Reference no.: 110. (Box-folder 17/9)
      - Miss Bliss., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 109. (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Modern jazz writer., Condensed score (sketch); 2 p.; 21 x 23.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil.; Reference no.: 233. (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Modern jazz writer., Piano part; 2 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Manuscript in ink in unknown hand, and holograph markings in pencil.; Reference no.: 233. (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Modern rhythms., Condensed score; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Montage., Cello part; 4 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 211. (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Moon light., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verson: the tune Lett, scratched out. (Box-folder 18/5)
      - My city., Chord chart; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 18/6)
      - Myself when I am real., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 154. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music.; Reference no.: 053. (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Myself when I am real., Condensed score; 9 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in ink by H.B. Miller, with holograph markings in pencil.; Reference no.: 053. (Box-folder 37/14)
      - Myself when I am real., Condensed score; 9 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of manuscript in ink by H.B. Miller; photocopy is smaller in size than original and contains additional markings.; Reference no.: 053. (Box-folder 18/8)
      - Myself when I am real., Clarinet part; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink.; Reference no.: 053. (Box-folder 18/9)
      - N.B.C. documentary See also: Where does a man go to find peace, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 160. (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Nacirema., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil.; Reference no.: 236. (Box-folder 18/11)
      - New Foundland., Full score; 24 leaves; 39 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 054. (Box-folder 38/1)
      - New York sketch book., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 156. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 18/12)
      - No. 1., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 058. (Box-folder 18/13)
      - No. 1 grandson / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 7 leaves; 36 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 045.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 38/2)
      - No. 1 grandson (#16) / Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 045.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 18/14)
      - No. 2 (rebop and bebop)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 046. (Box-folder 18/15)
      - No. 3 (opus 3)., Chord chart; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 059. (Box-folder 18/16)
      - No. 3 (opus 3)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holograph and copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 059. (Box-folder 18/17)
      - No where., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 188. (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Nobody knows the Bradley I know., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © April 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 122. (Box-folder 18/19)
      - Nobody knows [the Bradley I know]., Full score (incomplete); [6] p.; 28 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 122. (Box-folder 38/3)
      - Nobody knows [the Bradley I know]., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 122. (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Noddin' ya head blues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink.; Reference no.: 056, 057, 224. (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Noddin' ya head [blues]., Full score; 2 p.; 28 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Paul Jeffrey.; Reference no.: 056. (Box-folder 38/4)
      - Noddin' ya head blues., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil, and photocopies of holographs.; Reference no.: 057. (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Noddin' ya head blues / Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscrip mt in ink with markings in pencil.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 18/23)
      - [Nostalgia in Times Square] (Strollin') / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 16 leaves; 36 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson. Title at head: Strollin'.; Reference no.: 148.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 38/5)
      - [Nostalgia in Times Square] (Strollin') / Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 149.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Nourog., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 157. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music.; Reference no.: 047, 272, 283. (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Nouroog., Full score; 19 leaves; 53.5 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 283. (Box-folder 43/7)
      - Nouroog., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 047. (Box-folder 18/26)
      - O.P. (also "O.P. Jr."), Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom: © June, 1974, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, NY.; Reference no.: 155, 273. (Box-folder 18/27)
      - O.P., Full score; 29 leaves, in 2 folders; 43.5 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's mauscript.; Reference no.: 273. (Box-folder 38/6-7)
      - Of love, pain, and passioned revolt ...., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Full title: Of love, pain, and passioned revolt, then farewell my beloved until it's Freedom Day. (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Oh Lord, don't let them drop that atomic bomb on me., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Nov. 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY. (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Once upon a time there was a holding corporation called Old America., Trumpet 1 part; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Open letter to Duke., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 240. (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Opus 4., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jan. 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY. (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Orange., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 32.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Orange., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink with pencil markings. (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Orange was the color of her dress, then pink., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 060. (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Orange (also orange was the color of her dress, then silk blues)., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © January 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 060. (Box-folder 19/9)
      - Orange orange was the color of her dress, then silk blues., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil, photocopies of holographs, and copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 060. (Box-folder 19/10)
      - Osmotin., Full score; 21 leaves; 53.5 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of holograph. Alternate title: Monk, Bunk, and visa versa.; Reference no.: 278. (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Our last kiss., Full score (incomplete); 5 leaves; 30.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 137. (Box-folder 38/9)
      - Pansies., Condensed score; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 19/11)
      - Paris in blue., Piano part (incomplete); 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink.; Reference no.: 183. (Box-folder 19/12)
      - Parkeriana., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 19/13)
      - Part II - of what?, Condensed score; 9 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings. (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Passions of a women loved., Lead sheet; 3 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink.; Reference no.: 180. (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Passions of a women loved., Chord chart; 8 p.; various sizes.; Note:L Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 180. (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Peddal point blues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 160. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Peggy's blue skylight., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph and photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom of copyist's manuscript: © October 1960, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 061. (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Peggy's blue skylight., Condenzed score; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 061. (Box-folder 19/19)
      - Peggy's blue skylight., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil, copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil, and photocopies.; Reference no.: 061. (Box-folder 19/20)
      - Percussion discussion., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., December 7, 1976.; Reference no.: 107. (Box-folder 19/21)
      - Percussion discussion (Percussion day)., Full score; 22 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 107. (Box-folder 44/1)
      - Percussion discussion., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink; includes photocopies.; Reference no.: 107. (Box-folder 19/22)
      - Pilobolus., Full score; 11 p.; 28.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil with some markings in ink.; Reference no.: 064. (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Pilobolus., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 064. (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Please don't come back from the moon., Full score; 22 leaves, in 2 folders; 34 x 46 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript. This item is seriously damaged and requires conservation treatment.; Reference no.: 287. (Box-folder 39/2-3)
      - Please don't come back from the moon., Piano part; 4 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript and holograph in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 023. (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Please don't come back from the moon (section II)., Full score; 15 leaves; 53 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 276. (Box-folder 39/4)
      - Please - play., Tenor part; 1 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 19/25)
      - Portrait., Lead sheets (2 versions); 2 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in pencil; one version in the hand of Sabu Adeyola, the other in the hand of Jimmy Knepper.; Reference no.: 065, 066, 067, 140. (Box-folder 20/1)
      - Portrait., Lead sheet (fragment); 2 p.; 32.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 067. (Box-folder 20/2)
      - Portrait., Chord chart; 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink. On verso: chord chart for the tune Orange.; Reference nos.: 065, 066, 067, 140. (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Portrait., Condensed score; 2 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and colored pencil in the hand of Bill Furioso.; Reference nos.: 065, 066, 067, 140. (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Portrait., Full score; 7 leaves; 26.5 x 56 cm.; Note: Holograph in regular and colored pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 208. (Box-folder 20/5)
      - Portrait., Full score; 13 p.; 34 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil with holograph markings in pencil.; Reference no.: 065. (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Portrait / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 8 leaves; 35.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 39/5)
      - Portrait., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink; one cello part on transparent paper.; Reference no.: 067. (Box-folder 20/7)
      - Portrait (#9)., Full score; [6] leaves; 28.5 x 35.5 cm. (in mylar).; Note: Holograph in pencil with holograph markings in colored pencil.; Reference no.: 140. (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Portrait (#9)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 066. (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Portrait (insert)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink with holograph pencil markings. (Box-folder 20/10)
      - Portrait (Make believe)., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 20/11)
      - [Portrait (variation)]., Trumpet part; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Prayer for passive resistance., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November 1976, NYC, NY. (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Prisoner of love., Full score; 6 leaves; 35.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 069. (Box-folder 39/6)
      - Profile of Jackie., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 116. Stamped: Blue Team Music Ed. Mus. (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Profile of Jackie McLean., Lead sheet (alto sax part); 2 p.; 27.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink with holograph pencil markings. On verso: Chord progressions to unknown composition, possibly Profile of Jackie McLean. (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Purple heart., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom of second p.: © February 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 070. (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Purple heart (#24)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and colored pencil.; Reference no.: 070. (Box-folder 20/17-18)
      - Pussy cat dues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom: © September 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 20/19)
      - Reincarnation [of a lovebird]., Piano score and lead sheet; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript in unknown hand.; Reference no.: 072. (Box-folder 20/20)
      - Reincarnation of a lovebird., Lead sheets "A" and "B"; 1 + 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of two manuscripts in unknown hand. Lead sheet "A" marked at bottom in pencil: Woman's key. Lead sheet "B" unmarked.; Reference no.: 072. (Box-folder 20/21)
      - [Reincarnation of a lovebird]., Lead sheet, with chord indications; 1 p.; 27.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in ink by Bill Furioso. Title at head: "Changes to Lovebird".; Reference no.: 072. (Box-folder 20/22)
      - Reincarnation of a lovebird., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil with holograph markings in pencil and ink, photocopies of holographs, copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil, and photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 072. (Box-folder 20/23)
      - Reincarnation of a lovebird (#22)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink with red pencil markings.; Reference no.: 071. (Box-folder 21/1)
      - Remember Rockefeller at Attica., Trumpet part; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink.; Reference no.: 223. (Box-folder 21/2)
      - [Remember Rockefeller at Attica (Just for laughs saps)]., Condensed score; 2 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At head: Alternate title Just for laughs scatched out.; Reference no.: 293. (Box-folder 21/3)
      - [Remember Rockefeller at Attica (Just for laughs saps)]., Chord chart; 2 leaves 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 293. (Box-folder 21/4)
      - [Remember Rockefeller at Attica] (Just for laughs saps)., Instrumental parts; 2 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscipts; notation and markings in unknown hand. At head: Just for laughs.; Reference no.: 293. (Box-folder 21/5)
      - Revelations., Lead sheet; 7 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom of first leaf: © Nov. 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 073. (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Rhapsody ever after., Drum part; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript with holograph markings in ink and colored pencil. (Box-folder 21/7)
      - Roland Kirk's message., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November 1976, NYC, NY. (Box-folder 21/8)
      - Rotatin'., Condensed score; 2 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Saint and sinner join in merriment on battle front: from The black saint., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript in unknown hand. At bottom: © Dec. 1975, Jazz Workshop., Inc., New York, NY. (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Sally wanna doodle all day., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 237. (Box-folder 21/11)
      - Scenes in the city., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 163. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. Stamped: Blue Team Music Ed. Mus. (Box-folder 21/12)
      - School boy., Condensed score; 3 leaves; 39.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil with ink markings.; Reference no.: 118. (Box-folder 39/7)
      - School boy., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 165. (Box-folder 21/13)
      - [Search the beyond]: written "Search the beond"., Condensed score; 1 p; 27.5 x 34.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Item includes additional notation on attached pages. (Box-folder 21/14)
      - Self-portrait in three colors., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 074. (Box-folder 21/15)
      - Self-portrait in three colors., Full score; 5 leaves; 22.5 x 34.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 074. (Box-folder 21/16)
      - Self-portrait in three colors., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 074. (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Self-portrait in three colors., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 074. (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Septemberly., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., December 7, 1976, New York, N.Y. (Box-folder 21/19)
      - [Shadows - themes]., Trombone part; 5 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and red pencil.; Reference no.: 219. (Box-folder 21/20)
      - She's just Miss Popular hybrid., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November 1976, New York, N.Y. (Box-folder 21/21)
      - Shoes of the fisherman's wife: a.k.a. Once upon a time there was a holding corporation called Old America., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom: © Dec. 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc. NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 080, 081. (Box-folder 21/22)
      - Shoes of the fisherman's wife / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 47 p.; 48.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson; includes photocopied pages.; Reference no.: 081.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 44/2)
      - Shoes of the fisherman's wife / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 46 leaves, in 2 folders; 35.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of manuscript by Sy Johnson with markings in blue ink.; Reference no.: 081.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 39/8-9)
      - Shoes of the fisherman's wife., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (4 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with color pencil markings.; Reference no.: 080. (Box-folder 21/23-26)
      - Shuffle bass boogie., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink. At bottom: © Sept. 1981, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, NY. (Box-folder 22/1)
      - Sketch #1 / music by Charles Mingus; words by Susan Graham., Piano-vocal score; 6 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil; words in typescript. At bottom: © Jazz workshop, Inc., New York, 1978.; Reference no.: 075.; Access points: Graham, Susan Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Sketch #1 / music by Charles Mingus; words by Susan Graham., Piano-vocal score; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink; words in pencil.; Reference no.: 075.; Access points: Graham, Susan Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 22/3)
      - Sketch #1 (Sweet sucker dance)., Piano score; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with holograph markings in pencil. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 079. (Box-folder 22/4)
      - Sketch #2., Piano score; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., April 1978.; Reference no.: 206. (Box-folder 22/5)